Hi, my name is Mary Thinnes and I'm a skin care expert.
We discuss with you now pre, pre-peel instructions that are appropriate for getting the best results.
You want to actually prep your skin two weeks prior to getting your first chemical peel.
And by prepping the skin at home what I mean is, you know, if you have hyper pigmentation you want to use your lightning creams that I mentioned before.
You also want to start doing your papayas, papayas at home.
You can actually do this at home and leave it on for twenty minutes without steam and that actually will help break up those dead skin cells.
Obviously you don't want to do this every night because then you will get a really deep peel when you actually do the peel.
You want to do it like once every third night and the papaya maybe twice a week for those two weeks.
Also you want to stay out of the sun.
Tanned skin actually is not a good skin to do a peel on or burned skin for that matter because its so sensitive.
You also don't want to do any, any waxing prior to getting a peel.
And those are just things you to need to keep in mind before actually doing a chemical peel.